Guide to the National Education Association-Film, Audio, and Video records, 1938-2011 NEA1010.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Promotional Material, 1938-2011, bulk 1954-2011; 1954-2011; Series 3; 187 Linear Feet
  - Population Story, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4020, Folder 8)
  - Portrait of a $10,000 Teacher, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 1)
  - The Present is Prologue - Discussion, ca. 1966; Series 3; Magnetic audio tape, 7 1/2 IPS. (Box 3686, Folder 6)
    Discussion of the NASSP Internship Project; companion to "The Present is Prologue" film.
  - President Johnson at Crossland Vocational School Dedication, 1967; series 3 (Box 4525, Folder 1)
  - President Keith Geiger: "Greetings" & "ESP", April 2, 1990; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3985, Folder 5)
  - President Johnson: Teacher in the White House 1, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 2)
  - President Johnson: Teacher in the White House 2, 1965; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 3)
  - President Johnson: Teacher in the White House 3, 1965; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 4)
  - President Johnson: Teacher in the White House 4, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4058, Folder 20)
  - Presidential Inaugural Parade Activities Roll 1, January 20, 1993; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4009, Folder 10)
  - Presidential Inaguration Parade Activities Roll 3, January 20, 1993; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4010A, Folder 1)
  - President Reg Weaver Radio Spots, September 2004-June 2005; Series 3; DVD (Box 4015, Folder 33)
  - President Reg Weaver Radio Spots, September 2004-June 2005; Series 3; DVD (Box 4015, Folder 34)
  - President's Committee film - Kennedy", undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3986, Folder 8)
  - Price Tag For Toby, May 1963; Series 3; Filmstrip; 33 1/3 RPM vinyl record. (Box 3677, Folder 8)
  - Prince Edward Co. VA Pacemaker, 1964; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3986, Folder 3)
  - Prince George's County - Teachers Collective Bargaining #2, April 18, 1990; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3989, Folder 7)
  - Profession of Politics, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 5)
  - Profile of Newt Gingrich from Frontline, January 16, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3981, Folder 3)
  - Promises to Keep, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 6)
  - Proposition 174: A Risk We Can't Afford, Circa 1993; Series 3; VHS Cassette Tape (Box 5081, Folder 2)
  - PSA's "Bus Driver", "Cafeteria", "All Jobs", March 1989; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4010A, Folder 2)
  - PSEA - Owen J. Roberts H.S. Stroke Interior - Meeting with B. Chase, May 8, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4010A, Folder 3)
  - Publi-Cable Seminar - Fred Friendly, undated; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4031, Folder 1)
  - Public School and Life of Community - Tape 6 The Public Schools and the Life of the Community - Warner Bloomberg, Jr. - Dean R.F. Campbell, William D. Firman - 0024, Undated; Series 3; 7 1/2 IPS (Box 3616, Folder 11)
  - Public Service Radio Spots: America's Children/Class Excursion, Undated; Series 3; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, no indicated speed. (Box 3703, Folder 3)
  - Public Service Radio Spots: Children are the Future/Next Generation, undated; Series 3; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 7 1/2 IPS. (Box 3703, Folder 1)
  - Questions to Grow On, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3981, Folder 3)
  - The Quiet Revolution, 1967; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 7)
  - Quiet Revolution, Undated; Series 3 (Box 4058, Folder 1)
  - RAFE, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 8)
  - Ray's Rell: Imagine, School Days, Make it Happen II, I, Invest in our Kids, July 1, 1992; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4029, Folder 8)
  - Read Across America 1999 PSA - Danny Glover, Honorary Chair, Series 3; CD-ROM (Box 4015, Folder 35)
  - Read Across America 2000 (5 Radio PSA's) 1, Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 13)
  - Read Across America 2000 (5 Radio PSA's) 2, Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 14)
  - Read Across America 2000 (5 Radio PSA's) 3, Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 15)
  - Read Across America 2001 "Public Service Campaign" 1, December 13, 2000; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4010A, Folder 3)
  - Read Across America 2002 "VEA Salutes the V.A. Symphony", March 29, 2002; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4010A, Folder 5)
  - Read Across America 2002 "VEA Salutes US Navy USS George Washington", April 4, 2002; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4010A, Folder 6)
  - Real Self, 1970; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 9)
  - Reg Footage, July 18, 2008; Series 3; DVD-R (Box 4015, Folder 36)
  - Reg Weaver- Biography Video, March 2008; Series 3; DVD (Box 4015, Folder 37)
  - Reg Weaver, Interview, NEA Minority Presidents, February 22, 2008; Series 3; Weaver, Reginald; Two audio cassette tapes. (Box 3682, Folder 69)
  - Reorganized Intermediate School Districts in Iowa, Undated; Series 3; film (Box 3656, Folder 2)
  - Rep. Robert Matsui, June 20, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4013, Folder 6)
  - Report on Tomorrow, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 10)
  - Research - "Education Finance: Foundation for America's Future", September 4, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3985, Folder 6)
  - Retirement and Benefits Advocacy Program: Protecting and Enhancing the Retirement Security of Education Employees, Undated; Series 3; VHS Cassette Tape (Box 5081, Folder 8)
  - Right Angle 1, 1959; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 11)
  - Right Angle 2, 1959; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 12)
  - Ron Brown Thanks the NEA, November 12, 1992; Series 3 (Box 3989, Folder 10)
  - Ross School Shoot (B.J. Ventser CET), June 10, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4020, Folder 9)
  - Roy S. Erlandson Recalls Days at NEA, September 17, 1969; Series 3; Erlandson, Ray S.; Magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. (Box 3688, Folder 7)
    1st NEA Asst. Secretary (in charge of business) (1919-1922), Roy S. Erlandson recalls days at NEA and visits with Miss Alice Morton of NEA Archives on Sept. 17, 1969. The last few minutes are with Gladys West of AASA--employed with NEA since 1923--in recent years as convention coordinator for AASA.
  - Running for Office 1992, March 25, 1992; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4029, Folder 9)
  - Rush Limbaugh KCOP Ch. 13, July 7, 1994; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4020, Folder 10)
  - Safe Schools Event - NEA RA 2000, September 5, 2000; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3981, Folder 4)
  - Sarah Pasma - Future Teachers of America, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 45)
  - Sarah Pasma - Future Teachers of America, undated; series 3 (Box 4549, Folder 1)
  - Saratoga B-Roll, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4010A, Folder 8)
  - Saratoga Elementary "Free at Last" Interviews, June 12, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4010A, Folder 8)
  - Saratoga Elementary Interviews (cont.), June 12, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4010A, Folder 9)
  - Saratoga Elementary Interviews (cont.) B-Roll, June 12, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4010A, Folder 10)
  - Sat. Morning Season: Panel, Undated; Series (Box 4033, Cassette 3)
  - Satellites, School & Survival, 1960; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 14)
  - Satellites, School & Survival, 1960; series 3 (Box 4535, Folder 2)
  - Saturn, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4011, Folder 1)
  - The Scholar, August 25, 1966; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 13)
  - School Board Meeting Interview "Beauty Shots" Mobile, Ala. Tape #3, March 28, 1990; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4021, Folder 1)
  - Selling The Association Tips, Undated; Series (Box 3849, Film 1-inch type data_value_missing_00691201f27ef2cb803ac408cafc3276)
  - Schoolhouse in the Red, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 14)
  - Schools Come First, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 33)
  - Schools Come First, undated; series 3 (Box 4556, Folder 1)
  - School Teacher, November 7, 1957; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 15)
  - School Teacher (Danny Thomas), January 7 1957; series 3 (Box 4582, Folder 1)
  - School Year, 1958; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 16)
  - School Year, 1958; series 3 (Box 4576, Folder 1)
  - Second Classroom, undated; series 3 (Box 4563, Folder 3)
  - Secret of Freedom - Spot, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 46)
  - Secret of Freedom - Spot, undated; series 3 (Box 4550, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Education Richard W. Riley - NEA Board of Directors Meeting, October 16, 1993; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3990, Folder 8)
  - Secretary Network, December 1, 1986; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4029, Folder 10)
  - Section 10, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 34)
  - Section 10, undated; series 3 (Box 4557, Folder 1)
  - Secure the Blessings, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4058, Folder 2)
  - See How They Learn 1, 1956; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 15)
  - See How They Learn 2, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4058A, Folder 1)
  - Sen. Ed Kennedy, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 30)
  - Sen. Tsongas, November 19, 1991; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4011, Folder 3)
  - Shirley Temple TV Spot, November 6-12, 1960; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 29)
  - Sistema de Evaluacion de Trabajo, April 6, 1989; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4011, Folder 2)
  - A Shoebox Full of Dreams, 1956; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 16)
  - Shooting for Success, April 19, 1989; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3985, Folder 7)
  - Sould I Know My Child's IQ?, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4058B, Folder 3)
  - Site-based, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3981, Folder 5)
  - Site-based Decisions, October 27, 1989; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3981, Folder 6)
  - Skippy and the Three R's 1, 1953; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 17)
  - Skippy and the Three R's 2, 1953; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 17)
  - Skippy and the Three R's 3, undated; Series 3 (Box 4058, Folder 17)
  - Small Miracles (Generics) 4 cuts, June 15, 1993; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4029, Folder 11)
  - Small Miracles (Public Service No Logo), July 8, 1993; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4029, Folder 12)
  - Smart Thinking & Signs w/ NEA Logo, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4021, Folder 2)
  - SNA Tribute, June 5, 1995; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3985, Folder 8)
  - SNEA - Penn State, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 18)
  - Soaring - National TV Spot 2000 1, Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4011, Folder 4)
  - Soaring - National TV Spot 2000 2, Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4011, Folder 5)
  - Soaring - National TV Spot 2000 3, Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4011, Folder 6)
  - South Carolina NBC7 Report, "Supporting and Staffing High-Needs Schools", Undated; Series 3; CD-R (Box 4015, Folder 38)
  - South Dakota Educ. Assoc. - "Why #3", June 24, 1992; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3985, Folder 9)
  - Staff Party "Oh, Baby", 1994; Series 3 (Box 3991, Folder 4)
  - State Association NEA Co-op Advertising Program NEA 3581 "Legacy", NEA 3591 "Mrs. Jones", NEA 3601 "School Zone", NEA 2961 "Headlines", 1998; Series 3; VHS Cassette Tape (Box 5081, Folder 5)
  - State Leaders at White House, November 1963, Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 19)
  - State of the Union - Bill Clinton CNN, January 24, 1995; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3981, Folder 7)
  - The St. Louis Pres. PAAS, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 21)
  - Stock Footage - Phx. Skyline, February 28, 1990; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4011, Folder 7)
  - Story of a Trial, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4021, Folder 3)
  - Strategic Planning NEA Membership & Affiliates, January 10, 1992; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4029, Folder 12)
  - Strategic Work Team, May 1, 1992; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4029, Folder 14)
  - Strategic Work Team: Diversity Education in a Pluralistic Society, 1992; Series 3; VHS Cassette Tape (Box 5081, Folder 3)
  - Summer Harvest, 1962; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 22)
  - The Sword and the Quill, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 20)
  - "The System" (Stock # 382-11748) NEA - CSI, Undated; Series 3; 7" Reel 3-3/4 IPS (Box 3630, Folder 11)
  - Tabco "Unity...", September 8, 1992; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4021, Folder 4)
  - Talks on Tape: Ole Sand Cassette (Stock # 382-11766), Undated; Series 3 (Box 3616, Folder 12)
  - The Talented, The Gifted and the Genius, undated; series 3 (Box 4570, Folder 1)
  - Tape 1 CSI Staff Mtng, 10/28; Series (Box 4033, Cassette 4)
  - Tape 2 CSI Forum Assersment W/ Pom Ashbcnen, Undated; Series (Box 4033, Cassette 6)
  - Tape II SRI contd; Grant Info, Undated; Series (Box 4033, Cassette 7)
  - Tape 2 CSI Staff Mtng., Undated; Series (Box 4033, Cassette 10)
  - Tape 1 - The Public School and The Life of Community - Henry Steele Commanger - 0019, April 26, 1965; Series 3; 7 /2 IPS (Box 3628, Folder 1)
  - Tape #1 - New Priorities, January 21, 1992; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4021, Folder 6)
  - Tape 2 - The Public School and The Life of Community - Terry Sanford, Governor North Carolina 0020, April 26, 1965; Series 3 (Box 3616, Folder 14)
    Sanford, Terry
  - Tape #2 - New Priorities, January 21, 1992; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4021, Folder 6)
  - Tape 3 - The Public School and The Life of Community - Edward J. Logue - 0021, April 26, 1965; Series 3 (Box 3630, Folder 1)
  - Tape 4 - The Public School and The Life of the Community - Commissioner Francis Keppel - 0022, Undated; Series 3; 7 1/2 IPS (Box 3630, Folder 2)
    Keppel, Francis
  - Tape 5 - The Public School and The Life of the Community - "Who Makes the Decisions about Public Schools" H. Thomas Hames - 0023, Undated; Series 3; 7 1/2 IPS (Box 3630, Folder 3)
  - Tape 7 - The Public School and The Life of the Community - Public Schools Congresswoman Patsy Mink and Carl T. Rowan - 0025, Undated; Series 3; 7 1/2 IPS (Box 3630, Folder 4)
  - Tape 8 - The Public School and The Life of the Community - Harry Golden - 0026, April 26, 1965; Series 3; 7 1/2 IPS (Box 3630, Folder 5)
  - Tape 9 - The Public School and The Life of the Community - "The Meaning of Equality in Education" Melvin M. Tumin - 0027, April 27, 1965; Series 3; 7 1/2 IPS (Box 3554, Folder 1)
    Offsite in a shared box with box 3554, 3653, 3649, 3654, 3655, 3648, 3651, 3645, 3644
  - Tape 10 - The Public School and The Life of the Community - "The Meaning of Equality in Education" Comments Supt. Carl F. Hansen, Fritz Redl. - 0028 # 10, April 27, 1965; Series 3; 7 1/2 IPS (Box 3630, Folder 6)
  - Tape 11 - The Public School and The Life of the Community - "The Meaning of Equality in Education" Comments, Dr. Book binder, Dr. Deutch, Asst. Supt. Shepard. Jr - 0029, April 27, 1965; Series 3 (Box 3630, Folder 7)
  - Tape 12 - The Public School and The Life of the Community - George H. Gallup 0030, April 27, 1965; Series 3; 7 1/2 IPS (Box 3630, Folder 9)
  - Teacher Accused, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4058B, Folder 2)
  - Teacher Corps, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 24)
  - Teacher Interviews, December 5, 1967; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 20)
  - "The Teacher is Between" Black/White Length: 15:00, Undated; Series 3; 16 mm film (Box 3554, Folder 4)
    Offsite in a shared box with box 3554, 3653, 3649, 3655, 3648, 3651, 3645, 3644, 3635
  - "The Teacher is Between" Black/White Length: 15:00, Undated; Series 3; 16 mm film (Box 3554, Folder 5)
    Offsite in a shared box with box 3554, 3653, 3649, 3654, 3648, 3651, 3645, 3644, 3635
  - Teacher of the Year, 1965; series 3 (Box 4563, Folder 2)
  - Teacher of the Year Interview - Mary Beth Blegen, May 7, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4011, Folder 8)
  - "The Teacher" (Stock # 382-11744) NEA- CSI, Undated; Series 3; 7" Reel 3-3/4 IPS (Box 3630, Folder 12)
  - Teaching the One and the Many, 1968; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 25)
  - Teacher's Career C-54, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 23)
  - Teachers in Politics 1, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3986, Folder 9)
  - Teachers in Politics 2, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3993, Folder 1)
  - Teachers Make a Difference, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3993, Folder 2)
  - Teachers Strike, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3993, Folder 3)
  - Teaching the One and the Many, 1968; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3993, Folder 5)
  - Teacher TV Open, January 16, 1992; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4021, Folder 7)
  - Teacher TV "The Look", January 24, 1994; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4021, Folder 8)
  - Teaching in The Middle School, Undated; Series (Box 3849, Film 1-inch type data_value_missing_e5e46e55c045d401280d955feabcbf6d)
  - Teachers Working with Parents, Undated; Series (Box 3849, Film 1-inch type data_value_missing_0e3f8401f8f7a96e816f979502158a16)
  - Teacher's Role in Student Motivation, Undated; Series (Box 3849, Film 1-inch type data_value_missing_a50224a046bdf70eb8f1c5ddf3549872)
  - Teaching Learning Disabled Students, Undated; Series (Box 3849, Film 1-inch type data_value_missing_e328fe71267c368f6f841c35e370dc14)
  - Teaser for Parents Ask About School, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3993, Folder 4)
  - Teen Talk: Elmo Ousley, Teacher of the Year, 1963; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3993, Folder 6)
  - Tennessee Delegate Questions Clinton, July 7, 1992; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4029, Folder 15)
  - Terry Herndon Interview by Al-Tony Gilmore, September 21, 2010; Series 3; Herndon, Terry; Two audio cassette tapes and manuscript notes from interview. (Box 3851, Folder 4)
  - Thirty Second Spot - "Get Involved" 1, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 22)
  - Thirty Second Spot - "Get Invloved" 2, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 26)
  - Thirty Second Spot - "Kids Grow Up" 1, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 23)
  - Thirty Second Spot - "Kids Grow Up" 2, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 24)
  - Thirty Second Spot - "Randy", undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 25)
  - Those Who Care, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3993, Folder 7)
  - Those Who Care, 1970; series 3 (Box 4541, Folder 3)
  - Those Who Care, 1970; series 3 (Box 4544, Folder 1)
  - Three to Make Ready, series 3 (Box 4588, Folder 4)
  - [Title illegible], Undated; Series (Box 4033, Cassette 8)
  - A Time for Talent 1, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 26)
  - A Time for Talent 2, 1961; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 27)
  - The Time of Their Lives 1, 1962; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 28)
  - The Time of Their Lives 2, 1962; Series 3 (Box 3992, Folder 29)
  - Time to Teach, undated; Series 3 (Box 3993, Folder 8)
  - They Grow Up So Fast, 1956; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3992, Folder 30)
  - Today's Education Annual Edition, 1983-4; Series 3; microfilm (Box 4030, Folder 3)
  - Today's Education (Elementary Edition) V. 69 1-4, February-December 1980; Series 3; microfilm (Box 4030, Folder 4)
  - Today's Education (General Edition) (1979 Index) V. 69 1-4, Debruary-December 1980; Series 3; microfilm (Box 4030, Folder 5)
  - Today's Education (Social Studies Edition) V. 69 1-4, February December 1980; Series 3; microfilm (Box 4030, Folder 6)
  - Treasury Tax Ruling, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 47)
  - Treasury Tax Ruling, undated; series 3 (Box 4552, Folder 1)
  - TSTA - Site-based Decisionmaking MASTER, 1991; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4011, Folder 9)
  - Twenty Cent Tip, undated; series 1 (Box 4529, Folder 1)
  - Twenty Years of Unity, May 1, 1986; Series 3; VHS videocasette, 15:14. (Box 3828, Folder 8)
  - Untitled, undated; series 3 (Box 4563, Folder 4)
  - Untitled, undated; series 3 (Box 4572, Folder 1)
  - Untitled BETACAM Cassette, Undated; Series 3; BETACAM Video Cassette Tape (Box 5081, Folder 1)
  - Untitled Video Tape Reel, Undated; Series 3 (Box 3853, Folder 7)
  - Up Memorial, October 24, 2001; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4013, Folder 7)
  - USAID "Lessons without Borders", October 3, 1994; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 24)
  - Value Education, May 2, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4011, Folder 10)
  - Value Education Sample Copy, 1997; Series 3; VHS Cassette Tape (Box 5081, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Beach Education Association "Individual Member Video", Ariel 15, 1994; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4012, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Beach Education Association: I Teach at the Beach "A Proud Tradition", undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4012, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Beach Education Association: I Teach at the Beach "A Proud Tradition We Must Continue", March 16, 1994; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4012, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Education Assoc. "Interface Video", undated; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 32)
  - Virginia Education Association, TV Ads, Undated; Series 3; DVD-R (Box 4015, Folder 39)
  - Visiting Day, 1959; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3993, Folder 9)
  - Walter Mondale (Minneapolis), February 3, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4012, Folder 4)
  - Walter Mondale Speaks About Ken Melley, February 7, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4021, Folder 9)
  - Walter Mondale Take Two, February 4, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4012, Folder 5)
  - Wanted: Cabinet Level Department of Education, 1978; Series 3; Filmstrip with audio cassette soundtrack. (Box 3685, Folder 1)
  - Wash-Post Mr. Geiger, June 11, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4021, Folder 10)
  - WA Summit Report, Undated; Series 3; CD-R (Box 4015, Folder 40)
  - Watch Out for Ollie, 1961; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 1)
  - Watch Out For Ollie, undated; series 3 (Box 4573, Folder 1)
  - We Hold These Rights, ca. 1968-1971; Series 3; Filmstrip; 33 1/3 RPM vinyl record. (Box 3680, Folder 3)
  - Western Match Excerpt - ABC, undated; series 3 (Box 4574, Folder 1)
  - Western Match Excerpt - ABC, undated; Series 3 (Box 3994, Folder 2)
  - We Teach the Children 1, Undated; Series 3 (Box 3657, Folder 1)
    Film Cannister and Audio cassette held in box 3656
  - We Teach the Children 2, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 27)
  - We Teach the Children - A 60 Second PSA from the NEA (Audio), Undated; Series 3; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, 7 1/2 IPS. (Box 3703, Folder 5)
  - We Teach the Children - A 60 Second PSA from the NEA (Film), Undated; Series 3; 16 mm film, 5400K. (Box 3703, Folder 6)
  - What Do I Get for my NEA Dues?, 1960; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 3)
  - What Do I Get for My NEA Dues?, 1960; series 3 (Box 4579, Folder 1)
  - What Greater Gift, 1953; series 3 (Box 4528, Folder 1)
  - What Is a School?, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 4)
  - What is a School?, undated; series 3 (Box 4578, Folder 1)
  - What Teachers Say: Class Size, 1977; Series 3; 4 Audio cassette tapes (Box 4032, Folder 5)
  - What Teachers Say: Mainstreaming, 1976; Series 3; 4 Audio cassette tapes (Box 4032, Folder 6)
  - What's Happening, undated; series 3 (Box 4518, Folder 1)
  - The White House, the School House: America's Future - Government Relations; Presidential Politics, 1991; Series 3 (Box 3991, Folder 10)
  - White House Reception, October 11, 1995; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4013, Folder 8)
  - Why Little Children Lose Out, undated; series 3 (Box 4588, Folder 2)
  - Who Is Pete?, 1961; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 5)
  - Who is Pete?, 1961; series 3 (Box 4577, Folder 1)
  - With A Single Voice, undated; series 3 (Box 4571, Folder 1)
  - Will We Have Year Round Schools?, 1961; series 3 (Box 4562, Folder 1)
  - Will We Have Year Round Schools?, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4058B, Folder 1)